Guide to the Office of Marketing and Communication records ARCH115
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
- Acc. 2013.30 (Box 1.1-3.2, Box 3.3-5.3, Box 6.1-7.3)
  Jablonowski, Marc
  Jacobs, Ranoly
  Jacob, Betty
  Jacobs, Randy (Faculty)
  James, Harvey
  Janssen, Priscilla
  Jassem, Harvey (M.) AandS (CAT)
  Jehenson, Y.
  Jemiolo, Robert
  Jolly, David (Hartt Faculty)
  Rolent Jessup
  Johnson, Allen G.
  Johnson, Scott
  Jones, Eleta PHD (Faculty)
  Board of Regents
  Kasclelny, Anne
  Box 4.2
  Kahn, Michael D. (Dr.)
  Kagan, Joel D. (Dr.)
  Kalb, Maruin
  Kalika, Peter, asst. dean Eng.
  Karr, Gary- Hartt
  Virginia, Hale
  Katrichis, Jerome
  Katz, Sandra
  Katz, Dr. William H.
  James Keener
  Kelly, Lynne
  Kelley, Oauy
  Kepner, Charlie
  Keshawarz, Mohammad (Faculty)
  Keshawarz, Saleh
  Kahn, Susan (Adjuct Faculty)
  John Kniering Staff
  Klippstatler, Kurt
  Box 4.3
  Kolluri, Bharat R. (Business School)
  Komisar-Blog and pix
  Youssef I. Kouatly
  Kraus, Eileen
  Lahey, Dr. Frank J.
  Lang, Robert
  La Rosa, Barbara
  Larson, John (Faculty)
  Lashigari, Malek K. (Dr.)
  Lawrence, Madelaine
  Lazier, Rebecca
  LeDoux, John
  Lee, James
  Lemnois, Andrew
  Leone, Donald J. Dr. (College of Engineering)
  Thomas F. Lepore (engineering)
  Dr. Robert M. Leve
  Levy, Miriam J.
  Lewis, Harrison – Faculty
  Li, Xiao Rong
  LiBassi, Peter
  Litchenstein, Benyamin (Faculty)
  Lilliguist, Nancy (Faculty)
  Loftus, Robert
  Box 5.1
  Logan, Robert A. III (Dr.)
  Loomis, Louise
  Luccarelli, Humbert
  Lyman, Peggy
  Macbride, David- Hartt Faculty
  Machell, Dave – Faculty
  David, Madsen
  Maguder, Theodore L.
  Malone, Michael R.
  Walter G. Markham, Associate prof. Dept. of Political Science 9-71
  Gerald Marks
  Marks, Lawrence
  Marks, Leta
  Markson, Stephen L.
  Martin, Linda – Faculty
  Dr. Richard S. Martin
  Martinkonic, Joseph
  Maslin, Adrienne Leinwand
  Massaro, John J., AandS '61
  Mastrianna, William
  Matacin, Mala L.
  Dr. James B. Mathews
  Box 5.2:
  McBryar, James A.
  McBride, David
  McCormick, Kathleen (Faculty)
  McLean, Jackie
  McDaniel, Prof. Elizabeth A., 1979-
  McEnteer, James B.
  McLean, Jackie (Hartt College)
  McGivney, Raymond J. Jr. (Dr.)
  Box 5.3
  Peter C. McLean
  McNamara, Regina
  McNevin, Valerie
  Messina, Natalie
  Minalek, Paul
  Milanovic, Ivana
  Milano, Edward J. (Ward)
  Miles, Wilford (Dean of Barney)
  Miller, L. Patrick (Hartt)
  Miller, Dr. Regina M. (Education)
  Faculty Misc.
  Morgan, Sandra – Faculty
  Mr. Watson Morrison
  E. Paul Moschella
  Lurai F. Motuiralla
  Mulready, Joseph F.
  Muppidi, Sundeep
  Murtha, Roger G. (Hartt)
  Myftaraj, Brunilda
  Nagurney, Ladimer (Faculty)
  Nadell, Pameta S.
  Nappier, Denise
  Niedenan, Reta
  Nott, Kenneth
  Sulayman Nyoung (Visiting Professor)
  O'Donnell, Sandra
  Ogilvie, John R. 1978-
  Oliver, Peter V. (Faculty)
  Orhon, Volkon
  Ogilvie
  Box 6.1
  Panik, Michael J. 1968
  Parker, Stephanie (Faculty)
  Pasquerella, Lynn
  Patti, Charles H.
  Pierce, Richard N.
  Pellecchia, Geraldine
  Pelto, Jonathan (adjunct faculty)
  Pence, Laura
  Pengel, Joachim E.
  Perez, Mrs. Carmen H.
  Stephen B. Peury
  Pertillar, Virginia
  Pesola, Tina
  Peters, Karl
  Karen Peterson
  Pines, David
  Pollina, Ann
  Pollina, Benedict J. (Math)
  Pomp, Richard
  Power Boothe Art School
  Pope, Sharon (Faculty)
  Porterfield, Sally
  Powell, Jack (Faculty)
  Powell, Orlo
  Provost, Richard
  Prior, Scott
  Pruett, Jerome- Hartt Faculty
  Prusank, Diane (Faculty)
  Pfiefer, Margret Francis
  Radonsky, Kenneth (Hartt)
  Ramsey, Clark
  Rassekh, Farhad (Faculty)
  Rauche, Anthony (Faculty)
  Reik, Cynthia (faculty)
  Richmond, Trudie
  Ritvo, Cynthia (Faculty)
  Rizzoti, Jennifer
  Robinson, Constance
  Robinson, Jackie
  Dr. Leo Rockas, full prof. 1971, Dept. of English
  Rogers, Annette
  Rogers, John
  Rohlfing, John
  Rooce, Michael
  Rosenfeld, Jonathan
  Rosenthal, Steven Ted (Dr.) AandS History
  Ross, Charles L. (Dr.)
  Roth, Lewis Richard
  Rottman, Leslie
  Rubinfeld, Sarah
  Russell, Ingrid (Faculty)
  Russell, Kristina Sandberg
  Charles Russo
  Reytman, Doza
  Salazar, Jr. Daniel (Faculty)
  Salinger, Barbara
  Box 6.2:
  Salowitz, Debra (Faculty)
  Sanders, Brauns William
  Sanders, Bill
  Sandstorm, Harald M. (Faculty)
  Sassi, Maria
  Saundersm Luann
  Saunders, Robert Jr.
  Schaffer, Marilyn C.
  John J. Schloss
  Schulze, Mary W. (Mrs.) (nursing)
  Myron Schwager (faculty)
  Seabury, John
  Seabury, Mancia
  Sellars, James – Hartt
  Shakupeare Symposium '84
  Sharpless, Thomas W. Chemistry Dept.
  Shattuck, James
  Sheldon, Michael
  Shepela, Sharon (Faculty)
  Shertukde, Hemchandra (Faculty)
  Shetty, Davis (Faculty)
  Silver-Bernstein, Carrie
  Silvester, Paul
  Dr. Tracy L. Simpson #15726
  Box 6.3
  Singamsetti, Dr. Rao N.
  Singer, David
  Singer, Joseph (Faculty)
  Kathleen H. Sloan
  Smith, Betsey (Faculty)
  Eueritt K. Smith, Jr. (Ward)
  Smith, Larry Alan- Dean of Hartt
  Smith, Dr. Leo T., 1978-
  Smith, Marilyn S. Mrs. (CBS) Philosophy
  Smith, Thomas N. (Arts and Sciences/ English)
  Smurthwaite, John (Faculty)
  Spacek, Jana
  Spaulding, Susan (Hartt fac.)
  Spence, Beverly
  Spreisterbach, Alal
  Craig Stalk- Eng.
  Ken Steen
  Paul Stacy (Faculty)
  Box 7.1 – 7.3
  Steinberg, Sharon
  Dr. Malcom P. Stevens, assoc. prof. Dept. of Chemistry 9-71
  Stevenson, Dr. Catherine Barnes
  Edward, N. Stevensen, Jr.
  Stewart, John
  Stinson, Lisa (Art Faculty)
  Streitfield, Barbara D. 1975
  Dr. Streifler, Manfred E.
  Suosky, Donald G. Reverend (Basic Studies/ Sociology/9/68)
  Edmond Sullivan (Former Faculty)
  Sullivan, John J.
  Susan Sullivan Glenney
  Sutton, Patricia L. faculty (Art)
  Sweitzer, Frederick –Faculty-
  Sypher, Howard E. (Dr.)
  Robert A. Tretreault
  Thompson, Bruce
  Tolo, Leland
  Tonkin
  H. Tonkin (Faculty)
  Toth, Benjamin (Faculty)
  Debois Traynum-Lindsey
  Turner, Charles (Faculty)
  Tuttle, Delaney Ann Mary
  Uras, H. Mehmet
  Box 7.2
  ?Urguhart, Esphyr
  Van Rynbach, Iris
  Venice, Janna
  Viereck, Bettina
  Vojtek, Bob
  Wahab, Mahamoud (Faculty)
  Walens, Susan
  Dr. Lewis N. Walker (Appointed Engineering Dean, 1982)
  Wallace, George
  Wallace, Robert B. (Arts and Sciences 1968)
  Walsh, John T.
  Washer, Steven (Faculty)
  Warren, C.J.
  Watson, David
  Harry O. Warren
  Weaver, Francoise D. French (9/68)
  Weber, James K. Jr. (Dr.)
  Weese, Dr. Samuel H., 1978-
  Weinsweig, S. Edward
  Welch, Jonathan B. (Business)
  Welb, David
  Box 7.3:
  Weise, Patty
  Notes from North House
  Alfred P. Werbner
  Werk, Mrs. Kay S. (Business School)
  Gladys Wheeler
  White, Alex (Faculty)
  Whittlesey, Deborah W.
  White, Stephen K. (Dr.)
  White, Richard
  R. Wickman
  Wilcox, Jeffrey T. (Director of Security)
  Wildenberg, Gerald (Dr.) AandS Math
  Willett, William (Hartt Faculty)
  Imanuel Willheim
  Williams, John
  Williams, Larry
  Williams, Raymond
  Willis, John
  Wilson, Dr. James
  Wilson, Dr, Thomas F., Jr. -1972-
  Witt, Barbara (Faculty)
  Wodiczko, Krzysztof
  Woldemikael, Tekle -Faculty
  Wolf, Gail
  Wood, John A.
  Mr. Stephen Wood H.A.S.
  Woodard, Carolyn (Faculty)
  Woodiel, Paul (Faculty)
  Workman, Dr. Harry J.
  Wosczyna-Birch, Karen
  Wright, Joseph E. (Dr.) AandS Sociology
  Wright, Sheila
  Yeannakis, Lynne (Assistant Prof. Management) Visiting
  Yeh, Chai-Lun (Faculty)
  Charles A. Yoerkie, Jr., Inst. in Mech. Engr. 9-71
  Dr. Lee W. Yosha
  Youn, Ted I.K. Director of Planning and Research
  Young, C.J.
  Young, Clay (Coach)
  Young, Milton A. Dr.
  Young, Winfield J. (Assistant Prof. Ward)
  Zaharis, Nicholas (Faculty)
  Zangrando, Joanna S. (Mrs.)
  Zei, John – Faculty
  Zeiser, Dorothy
  Zeiset, David B. (Art School)
  Mr. John H. Zele
  Zimmerman, Christopher
  Zimmerman, P.M. – Photographer
  Zotos, Gloria
- Acc. 2014.2 and 2014.3, Circa 1950 - circa 2014; Accession 2014.2 and 2014.3
  The accession is open to all researchers.
  The accession contains publications for various marketing publications for various offices, departments, and occassions as well as files on people who were profiled by the University of Hartford or any other publication. The names include those of regents, faculty, staff, alumni, speakers, and special guests among others. Some files include photographs.
  Arranged into two series: I. People Files, II. Publications.
  - People Files
    - A (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)
    - B (Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 8, Box 9)
    - C (Box 9, Box 10, Box 11, Box 12)
    - D (Box 12, Box 13, Box 14, Box 15)
    - E (Box 15, Box 16)
    - F (Box 16, Box 17, Box 18)
    - G (Box 18, Box 19, Box 20, Box 21)
    - H (Box 21, Box 22, Box 23, Box 24)
    - I (Box 24)
    - J (Box 24, Box 25)
    - K (Box 25, Box 26, Box 27, Box 28)
    - L (Box 28, Box 29, Box 30, Box 31, Box 32)
    - M (Box 32, Box 33, Box 34, Box 35, Box 36, Box 37, Box 38)
    - N (Box 38, Box 39)
    - O (Box 39, Box 40)
    - P (Box 40, Box 41, Box 42, Box 43)
    - Q (Box 43)
    - R (Box 43, Box 44, Box 45, Box 46)
    - S (Box 46, Box 47, Box 48, Box 49, Box 50, Box 51, Box 52, Box 53)
    - T (Box 53, Box 54, Box 55)
    - U (Box 55, Box 56)
    - V (Box 56)
    - W (Box 56, Box 57, Box 58, Box 59, Box 60)
    - Y (Box 60)
    - Z (Box 60)
  - Publications
    - 50th Anniversary, 2007 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Athletics, 1999 - 2010, undated (Box 61, Folder 2-6)
    - Barney, 2004 - 2010, undated (Box 61, Folder 7-8, Box 62, Folder 1)
    - CETA (College of Engineering, Technology, and Architecture), 2000 - 2009 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Development, 1999 - 2010, undated (Box 62, Folder 3-7)
    - Educational Main Street (EMS), 1998 - 2002 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - ENHP (Education, Nursing, and Health Professions), 2000 - 2010, undated (Box 62, Folder 9-10)
    - Entrepreneurial Center, 2006 - circa 2014 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Graduate Programs, 2003 - 2010, undated (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Greenberg Center, 1998 - 2010 (Box 63, Folder 2-4, Box 66)
    - Handel Center, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Hartford Art School, 1999 - 2013 (Box 63, Folder 6-7, Box 66)
    - Hartford College for Women (HCW), 1998 - 2007 (Box 63, Folder 8-9)
    - Hartford Scholars Program, 2004 - 2010, undated (Box 63, Folder 10, Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Hartt, 1999 - 2009, undated (Box 64, Folder 2-4)
    - Hartt Community Division (HCD), 1999 - 2004, undated (Box 64, Folder 5-6, Box 66)
    - Hillel, 2003; circa 2009 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Hillyer College, 2001 - 2010, undated (Box 64, Folder 8-9)
    - Honorary Degrees, 2001 - 2009 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Human Resources (HRD), 1998 - 2010 (Box 64, Folder 11-12)
    - Institutional Advancement (IA), 2005; 2009, undated (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - International Center, Circa 2004 - 2009 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - ISET (Inteegrated Science, Engineering, and Technology Complex), 2005 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Joseloff Gallery, 2000 - 2002 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Magnet School, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Orientation, 1999 - 2010 (Box 65, Folder 6-7)
    - Parent Relations, 2004 - 2010, undated (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - President's Office, 1998 - 2010, undated (Box 65, Folder 9-11)
    - Public Safety, 2004 - 2009 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - UHSSE (University High School of Science and Engineering), 2005 - 2010, undated (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Ward College, 2001 - 2002, undated (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - WELFund (Women's Education and Leadership Fund), 2008 - 2010, undated (Box 65, Folder 15)
- Acc. 2016-01-12-02, 2001-2009; 0.21 Linear Feet (Box 1)
  This accession consists of records retained by Sharon Scorso. Almost the entire accession is regarding the Hartford College for Women (HCW) and its transition to the WELFund. One email correspondence is regarding a coin collection and the Sherman Museum.
  The accession is arranged into three files: General HCW, Articles and clippings, and Correspondence.
  Hartford College for Women
- Acc. 2016-03-02-02, 1956 - 2016 Jan; Bulk 1990-2005; 2016-03-02-02; 4.17 Linear Feet
  - University Notes (UNotes), 1990 Oct 17 - 2006 Feb 02 (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - New England Patriots Training Facility Proposal, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
  - Connecticut Conference of Independent Colleges (CCIC), 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Humphrey Tonkin, Circa 1997 - 1998 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
  - Presidential Search Committee, 1997, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - President Harrison, 1998-2007 (Box 3, Folder 10-14)
  - Inauguration, 1999 Mar - Apr (Box 3, Folder 15, Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Hartford Art School Inc. v. University of Hartford, 1992-2002, undated (Box 4, Folder 3-8)
  - Fuller Gift, 1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Situation Management Team Campus Emergency Plan [RESTRICTED], 2004 Oct (Box 4, Folder 10, Box 11)
  - Greenberg Center, 1999-2009 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Ward College, 1996-1999, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Emergency Prepardness and Response Plan [RESTRICTED], 2001 Sep - Nov (Box 5, Folder 4, Box 11)
  - Temple Street Project, Circa 2005 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Say Yes to Education, 1992-2005 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Thomas Cadillac Site and Hartt Gateway Center for Performing Arts Education, 2000-2002, undated (Box 5, Folder 7-9, Box 11)
  - CT Women Across Curriculum Throughout the Year, Teacher's Guide, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 10, Box 11)
  - Hartford College for Women (HCW) Merger, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Hartford College for Women (HCW) Entrepreneurial Center, 1996-1999, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Tipper Gore at Hartford College for Women (HCW), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Hartford College for Women (HCW) Discrimination Complaints [PARTIALLY RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
  - American Originals, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 6-11, Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Eunice H. Trowbridge, 1978, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Council for Advancement of and Support of Education (CASE), 1998-1999, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - All University Curriculum (AUC), Circa 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Office of Communication 2003 Plan (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Campaign for the University of Hartford, Circa 1997 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Tuition Letters, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Memorandums, and News Releases, 1992-1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Brochures and Folders, 2001-2007, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, 1989; 1992, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1956 - 2016 Jan; Bulk 1995 - 2016 Jan (Box 7, Folder 12-16, Box 8, Box 9, Folder 1-5)
  - Campaign of Commitment Communication Plan, 2002 Oct 10 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - ENHP History, 1968-2009 (Box 9, Folder 7-9)
  - 50th Anniversary Interviews, Circa 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Duplicates - University Notes (UNotes), 1995 Apr 5 - 2002 Nov 27 (Box 9, Folder 11, Box 10)
  - University of Hartford Banner (Box 12)
  - Media (VHS, DVD, CD, Floppy discs) (Box Shared CD Box 1, Box 11)
- Acc. 2017-10-25-01
  - Hartford Scholars, 1984 - 2010, undated (Box 1, Folder 1-14, Box 2, Folder 1-19)
  - Observer Images, 1997 May - 2002 Summer (Box 3, Folder 1 - 18, Shared Photograph Box 2, Box Shared Book Tray 2)
    This file consists of photographs, transparencies, slides, and other images used in printing the Observer. Also included, as part of the materials used for the Fall 2001 issue, is an uncorrected advance proof of "Masquerade" by Tivadar Soros, as translated by University President Emeritus Humphrey Tonkin.
  - New England Higher Education, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Budget Reports FY05 to FY10, 2005 - 2010 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Publications, 2003 - 2012 (Box 3, Folder 21, Box 4, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Women's Rights Symposium, 2007 March (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Photos, 1999, undated (Box 4, Folder 4 - 5)
  - Admissions Graduate and Part-Time Brochures, undated (Box 4, Folder 6, Box Shared CD Box 3)
    Floppy disks
  - Artifacts (Box 5)
    Includes a University of Hartford flag, a vertical felt banner featuring the University Seal, two bandanas, a T-shirt for UNotes, a small felt pennant, a pair of red and gray gym shorts, and a university of Hartford Frisbee.
  - Posters, 2004; 2014 Sep (Box Shared Oversized 1)
    Consists of two posters for "American Originals" and one for "Empowering Change."